剧情回顾...
因为瘫痪我坐了四年轮椅
I was in a wheelchair,paralyzed for four years.
这座岛改变了我
This island, it changed me.
让我充实
It made me whole.
十分感谢你 John
I'm so thankful for you, John.
你偷走了我的肾
You stole my kidney.
你需要一个父亲而我需要一个肾
You needed a father and I needed a kidney,
这就是现实
and that's what happened.
忘了它吧
Get over it.
我不在乎Jack怎么说
I don't care what Jack said.
我们必须救他回来这是我欠他的
They've got him, and we have to get him back. I owe him that.
你是怎么来这座岛的?
How did you get onto this island?
他们有一艘潜艇
They brought me on the submarine.
你们的人可以自由的来去吗?
So your people, they can just come and go whenever they want?
你永远不会知道一颗C4也能派上用处
You never know when a little c4 might come in handy.
姓名?
Name?
John Locke
婚姻状况呢 Locke先生?
Marital status, Mr. Locke?
单身
Single.
有女朋友吗?
Girlfriend?
没有
No
你的父母还活着吗?
Are your parents living?
我是被领养的 我从来没见过自己的父母
I was raised in foster care.I never really knew my parents.
你有没有想过 要寻找自己的亲生父母?
Have you ever considered seeking out your biological parents?
我认为这并不重要
I don't see how that's relevant.
这很重要Locke先生 因为如果政府要
It's relevant, Mr. Locke,because if the government's
继续支付你的残疾保险的话
gonna continue paying your disability insurance,
那我就要知道你的情况 是否有所改善
I have to figure out whether or not your condition has improved.
那么...你的胃口怎么样?
So... How's your appetite?
很好
Fine.
我发现你已经 停止支付你的医疗帐单了
I see you stopped submitting your therapy bills for reimbursement.
因为我已经不去了
It's 'cause I stopped going.
那只是浪费时间
Waste of time.
这只是临时的 Locke先生(停止残疾人保险)
It's just a temporary suspension,Mr. Locke.
一旦你重新接受治疗 你可以再来申请
As soon as you resume your sessions,you can reapply.
你认为我是暂时的残疾?
You think I'm temporarily disabled?
沮丧是暂时的 所以是的
Depression can be temporary, yes.
停止接受治疗真是明智之举
And since you see fit to stop going to therapy,I guess you're all better.
我猜是这样的
Guess I am.
下一个!
Next!
这边!
Over here!
他在做什么?
What is he doing?
好身手!
Good hands!
接的好
Nice.
她就是那个 帮助我和Sawyer逃跑的人
She's the one who helped me and Sawyer escape.
怎么了?
What's up?
我想还有段时间...
I think it's gonna be a while...
怎么了?
Hey, what?
John, Rousseau走了
John, Rousseau's gone.
这比我们想象的要复杂的多
This is gonna be more complicated than we thought.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧翻译组制作
YYeTs制作之美剧字幕首发网站 www.YYETS.com
翻译: 许愿   校对: 许愿
后期: 梁良   双语字幕: 端木首易 七色九天
我们就这样冲进去吗?
So you saying, we simply start shooting people and hope for the best?
我们是来救Jack的 现在可以行动了
We came here to rescue Jack,and we're gonna do it.
很明显情况有所改变
But obviously the circumstances have changed.
-他也许不想回来了  -那不是他
-He may not want to be rescued.  -That is not him.
那不是Jack
That's not Jack.
他们一定对他做了什么 我们被抓时也被下了药
They must have done some thing to him.When they captured us, they drugged us.
-他好像很清醒的样子  -他们绑架了他 把他当作囚犯
-He didn't appear to be drugged.  -They kidnapped him, held him prisoner.
-他是不会忘记的  -我同意
-He wouldn't just forget that.  -I agree,
但在没弄清楚前 我们不能冒生命危险
but until we know why,we're putting our lives at risk.
我不会留下他不管的 Sayid
I'm not leaving him, Sayid.
-我们还有选择  -这就是Jack
-We may not have a choice.  -It's Jack.
第一次见到他时 他冒着生命危险
The first time I saw him,he was risking his life
把受伤的人拖出飞机的残骸
pulling people out of burning airplane wreckage.
如果他现在和"the others"握手的话 我相信他有自己的理由
If he's shaking hands with the others,I'm sure he has a good reason.
我们只须过去查个究竟
We just have to go down there and find out what it is.
你有什么建议?
What do you suggest?
等天黑的时候 当Jack一个人时我们过去...
We wait till it's dark.We approach Jack when he's alone...
如果他想回来 我们就把他弄出来
And if he wants out, we get him out.
这就是我们所知道的
Here's what we know, Crystal.
昨晚两点左右 那笔玻利维亚的保险金被盗了
The bolivian coal deposits were stolen last night around 2:00 a.m.
那就意味着"眼镜蛇"又回来了
Oh, that means the cobra...he's back.
他被击中了吗?
Has he been shot?
我找不到他
I can't find him!
他有武器 我动不了了
He's armed! I can't get up!
你好 你是John Locke?
Hello. John Locke?
抱歉 谢绝推销
I'm sorry. No solicitors.
-有门上有标志  -我不是想要卖...
-I have a sign.  -I'm not trying to sell you...
听着 我叫Peter Talbot
Listen, my name's Peter Talbot.
我只想和你谈谈
I just need a couple minutes to talk to you.
关于什么?
Talk about what?
实际上 是我的母亲
My mother, actually.
我认为她和你遇到了同样的麻烦
I think she might be in some trouble.
我不是你要找的John Locke
You got the wrong John Locke.
你有几个肾脏?
How many kidneys do you have?
她是两个月前认识他的
She met him two months ago.
"一见钟情" 她是这样说的
"Love at first sight," is what she said.
那人很有魅力 很幽默
The guy was charming, sweet, funny.
他叫Adam Seward
His name's Adam Seward.
他是一个从安大略湖来的退休电脑承包商
He's a retired computer entrepreneur from Ontario.
Adam很特别
Anyway, Adam had something... special.
没过多久 我母亲就为他着迷了
My mom just went gaga for him right out of the gate.
在认识他两个月后 她答应嫁给他
After two months of knowing him,she agree to marry the guy.
而他的一些事情...
And something about him...
我认为他另有所图
Something in my gut told me that he was after something,
所以我就开始调查他
so I had to check him out.
我还是不知道 这和我有什么关系
Well, I'm not sure I know what any of this has to do with me.
这和你的确有关系 Locke先生
Well, what this has to do with you, Mr. Locke,
因为你捐了一个肾脏给Adam Seward
is that you donated one of your kidneys to Adam Seward,
只是那时他的名字不同罢了
only his name was different back then.
他曾用过"Anthony Cooper"这个名字
He used to be "Anthony Cooper."
我能找到的只有他的医疗记录
All I could find were his medical records,
我发现了他是一个肾脏移植的
and I saw that he was the recipient
接受者 当然是从你那里
of a kidney transplant from You.
我想 他骗走了别人的肾脏
So I figured, hey,someone gave the guy his kidney.
那该有多糟啊
How bad could he be?
是吗?
Right?
那是一个匿名捐赠
Well, it..it was an anonymous donation.
我从来没见过他
I never met him.
你确定吗?
Are you sure?
我很抱歉我帮不了你
Yeah, I'm sorry. I can't help you.
Sayid你守着前面
Sayid, you guard the front.
我到后面去掩护
I'll go around and cover the back.
你从侧门进去
You head in through the side door.
就我一个人进去?
I'm going in alone?
他第一个见到你更好
It's better if you're the first one he sees.
好吧
All right.
你在这里干什么?
What are you doing here?
我是来救你的
I came to get you.
马上离开这里
Get out of here
快走
right now. Go.
Kate 他们在监视我!
Kate, they're watching me!
-快离开这里!  -我不会离开你的
-Get out of here!  -I'm not leaving you.
-是的 你快走!  -趴下! 趴下!
-Yes, you are!  -Get down!
别伤害她!
Don't hurt her!
退后 医生
Step back, doc.
退后
Step back.
看住他
Hold him still.
和你们在一起的还有谁?
Who else is with you?
回答他的问题 Kate
Just answer the question, Kate.
再给你一次机会,还有谁?
Okay, one more time--who else is with you?
没人了
Nobody.
没人了 就我们两个
Nobody else. It was just us.
小声点
Keep your voice down.
好吧
All right.
没关系的 John
It's all right, John.
你不必用枪指着我
You don't have to point the gun at me.
我会告诉你Jack在哪儿的
I can tell you where Jack is.
我不是来找Jack的
I'm not looking for Jack.
我是来找那潜艇的
I'm looking for the submarine.
那艘潜艇
The submarine...
它在哪儿?
where is it?
我不知道你在说什么 John
I'm not sure what you mean, John.
什么潜艇?
What submarine?
那个可以帮你们离开这座岛的潜艇...
The one you use to travel to and from the island...
你们中的Mikhail告诉我的
The one your man Mikhail told me about
在他被我杀掉前
right before I killed him.
爸爸? 你在和谁说话?
Dad? Who are you talking to?
Alex 别进来!
Alex, don't come in here!
让她安静点
Tell her to be quiet.
Alex 求你了
Alex, please.
Ben 你醒了吗?
Ben, you awake?
我要进来了
I'm coming in.
什么事?
What is it?
是Austen和Jarrah
It's Austen and Jarrah.
他们在这里他们找到我们了
They're here. Somehow they found us.
他们现在在哪里?
Where are they now?
我们把他们关押在我的地方
We captured them.We're holding 'em over at my place.
要我帮你...
Want me to help you get out...
不 把他们分开 我要知道他们是怎么找到我们的
Separate them.I want to know how they found us.
那Juliet和Shepard呢?
What about Juliet and Shepard?
-明天...  -你别操心了 走吧
-Tomorrow...  -Let me worry about that. Just go.
好吧
Got it.
Richard 等一下
Richard, wait a minute.
我在外面等你
I'll wait outside.
我要你把从Tallahassee来的人带来
I want you to bring me the man from Tallahassee.
-你要他做什么?  -照做就是了
-What do you need him for?  -Just do it. Now.
好吧
All right.
"从tallahassee来的人"? 这是什么
"The man from Tallahassee"? What is that
一种暗号吗?
Some kind of code?
不 John 我们没有
No,John,unfortunately,we don't have a code
"有个男人在衣橱里用枪指着我女儿"这种暗号
for"there's a man in my closet with a gun to my daughter's head,"
很明显 我们应该有的
although we obviously should.
Sayid身上有个背包
He had a pack with him.
我要她帮我拿来
I want her to retrieve it.
好的
Okay.
但你应该知道John 我女儿最近很恨我
But you should know,John,my daughter currently hates me,
我不认为用她做人质 是明智的选择
so I'm not sure holding me hostage is your best option...
爸爸!
Dad!
我会帮你去拿的
I'll get your bag.
我在找那种惊艳的
I'm looking for something really stunning,
能吸引所有人眼球的那种
something that would grab everyone's attention on the table.
亲爱的 你觉得这朵怎么样?
Honey? What do you think of this one?
这看上去不错 你认为呢?
Oh, it looks good. What do you think?
我也很喜欢 但是是不是太大了
I like it.Maybe just a little larger.
还是大点的好
Larger would be good.
我去那边看看
I'll go over there and take a look.
你好 John
Hello, John.
你最近有喜事要办?
Gonna be a big to-do or just the two of you and a preacher?
我猜你不会邀请我的 因为当你介绍我时...
I guess you couldn't invite me, huh?That would make for...
会很尴尬的
awkward introductions.
你是怎么知道我...
How did you even know that I...
那是因为她儿子告诉我的
I know because her son came to me
还问我 我是怎么给你我的肾脏的
and asked why I gave you a kidney.
他知道你不怀好意 只是还没有证据
He's on to you,but he doesn't have any proof.
所以他来找我 让我作证
So he came to me hoping I would vouch for you.
你和他说了什么?
What did you say to him?
你在欺骗她 不是吗?
You're conning her, aren't you?
你和她结婚是为了她的钱
You're gonna marry her for her money, right?
你想干什么John?
What is it you want, John?
我要你结束这一切
I want you to end it.
我要你取消婚礼
I want you to call off the wedding.
你为什么要这样做?
Why are you doing this?
因为这不公平
Because it's not fair.
你让他们信任你
You make people think that you're their family,
然后逃之夭夭 还毁了他们的生活
and then you leave their life in ruins,
我是不会让你再这么做的
and I'm not gonna let you do it again.
你必须取消婚礼 然后离开
You're gonna call off your engagement and go,
否则我就告诉她真相
or I'm gonna tell her the truth.
我想听你自己说出来
I want to hear you say it.
你说你会离开的
You say you're gonna leave.
好吧 John
Okay, John.
我会的
You got it.
能帮我拿一下轮椅吗?
Would you mind helping me get into my chair?
我保证不耍花招
No tricks, I promise.
我只想得到些尊严
I just want some dignity.
你应该比任何人都明白我的意思吧
You of all people should understand what it means to want some dignity.
谢谢你
Thank you.
告诉我 John
So tell me, John,
你想怎么驾驶那潜艇?
how do you expect to pilot our submarine?
那是个很复杂的机械设备
I mean, it's a complicated piece of machinery.
不单单就是按"潜入"这么简单
You don't just press "submerge."
我会想办法的
I'll figure something out.
你知道 我曾是海军长官
For all you know,I was a commander in the navy.
抓住我的脖子 我来帮你起来
Put your arm around my neck.I'll lift under your knees.
那个包里是什么 John?
What's in the pack, John?
如果你见到了Mikhail 那就意味着你...
If you've met Mikhail, that means
去过那个通讯站...
you were in the communications station...
你就会找到炸药
Which means you found the explosives.
你不是想驾驶那潜艇离开这里 对吗?
So you're not planning to pilot the submarine anywhere, are you?
你是想炸毁它
You're planning to destroy it.
我了解你 John Locke
I know you, John Locke.
你什么都不知道
You don't know me at all.
我知道你在加州出生
I know you were born in California.
然后被领养
I know you were raised in foster care.
你在Tustin浪费了很多时间
I know you wasted a big part of your life in Tustin
只是在一个盒子公司里消磨自己的人生
pushing papers at a company that manufactured industrial boxes.
我还知道 在你没来这座岛的前四年间
I know you spent the four years
一直是靠坐轮椅的
prior to your arrival on this island in a wheelchair.
而且我知道是什么让你坐上那轮椅的
And I know how you ended up in it.
告诉我 John...
Tell me, John...
你痛苦吗?
Did it hurt?
我感到我的背被撕开了
I felt my back break.
你认为呢?
What do you think?
没想到那么快又见面了 Kate
I didn't think I'd see you again so soon, Kate.
小心点
Be careful in here.
谢谢
Thanks.
他们伤害你了吗?
Did they hurt you?
没有
No
你呢?
Did they hurt you?
没有
No
这些都是什么?
What is all this?
这就是他们住的地方
This is where they live.
那他们抓的人呢?
And the people they took?
孩子们呢?
The kids?
他们都很安全
They're all safe.
"安全"?
"Safe"?
你和他们现在是一伙的吗?
So you're with them now?
我不属于任何一方 Kate
I'm not with anyone, Kate.
他们对你做了什么?
What did they do to you?
-什么都没有  -那你为什么要这样?
-Nothing.  -Then why are you acting like this?
没有办法...
There's no way...
你...我没办法...
You... There's no way that I could...
我是来帮你的
I came here to help you!
你为什么不告诉我...
So why don't you tell me...
我告诉你不要回来找我
I told you not to come back here for me.
我不认为你是真心的
I didn't think you meant it.
他们对你做了什么 Jack?
What did they do to you, Jack?
我和他们做了笔交易
I made a deal with them.
他们会放我走的
They're gonna let me go.
去哪儿?
Where?
回家
Home.
什么时候?
When?
早晨的第一件事
First thing in the morning.
我会去找救援的 这是唯一的机会
I can bring back help.It's our best chance.
你相信这些人?
You trust these people?
他们是骗子 你为什么会相信...
They are liars. Why would you believe...
当你求我救Swayer的时候
I trust them because you told me to, Kate...
是你让我相信他们的 Kate
When you asked me to save Sawyer's life.
他们和你说了什么?
What did they tell you?
Jack 我们要走了
Jack, we need to go.
我一会儿就去
I'll be right there.
我让你不要回来找我 我也希望...
I asked you not to come back here for me, and I wish...
希望你不会来
I wish that you hadn't.
但我一定会回来找你的
But I will come back here for you.
John Locke?
Mason探长
Detective Mason.
这位是Reed探长 介意我们问你几个问题吗?
That's detective Reed. Do you mind if we ask you a few questions?
当然不
No, of course not.
你认识一个叫Peter Talbot的人吗?
Do you know a man named Peter Talbot?
不 我不认识
No, I don't think so.
偏瘦 棕色头发 大约20岁
Thin, brown hair, 20.
我们知道两天前他来过你的公寓
If it'll be helpful,we believe he was here in your apartment two days ago.
是的 他是个推销员
Yeah, he was a solicitor.
我把他轰走了
I sent him away.
Talbot先生家的资产有大约200万
Mr.Talbot's family is worth somewhere in the neighborhood of $200 million.
我很好奇 他怎么会去做推销员呢?
So I'm curious. What exactly was he selling you door-to-door?
我告诉过你了 我不认识他
Well, I...Look, I told you I don't know him.
那为什么他口袋里的纸上写着你的地址呢?
Then why was your name and address on a piece of paper in his pocket?
你们为什么会找他的口袋?
Why were you... would you be looking through his pockets?
因为Peter Talbot's已经死了
Because Peter Talbot's dead.
这不容易...
It wasn't easy, you know...
整天和你在你的舱里...
Being in that hatch with you all that time...
你总是走来走去
Knowing you had no business walking around,
如果我不告诉你我的真实身份 就连问你的资格都没有
knowing I couldn't even ask you about it without telling you who I really was.
现在你可以问我了...
So ask me now...
我已经知道你的真实身份了
Now that I know who you really are.
那很快吗?
Was it immediate?
你一来这个地方就开始了吗?
It started the moment you got here?
你就这样能走路了 就像人生的回归
And you were just walking,the feeling returned
就是坠机那天 对吗?
right after the crash, that day?
那就是"快"的意思 Ben
That's what "immediate" means, Ben.
你在想为什么你还不能恢复
You're wondering why it hasn't happened for you.
你的伤只能慢慢恢复
You're not recovering as fast as you like.
Jack帮你手术到现在多久了?
How long's it been since Jack fixed you?
一个星期?
A week?
我仔细一想
Now that I think about it,
原来你是怎么得病的?
how did you get sick in the first place?
你害怕那会消失吗 John?
Are you afraid it'll go away, John?
这就是你想炸毁那潜艇的原因吧!
Is that why you want to destroy the submarine?
因为你知道如果你离开这座岛
'Cause you know if you leave the island,
你又得回到轮椅上了
you'll be back in the chair?
你有吃的东西吗?
You got anything to eat?
回家去吧 孩子 你知道你不该在这儿的
Go on home,kid.You know you're not supposed to be here.
我父亲要我来拿他的包
My father sent me to get his pack.
为什么?
Why?
我不知道Ryan 但是他叫我来拿的
I don't know,Ryan,but he told me to get it.
好吧
All right.
拿去吧
Here you go.
你是Alex 对吗?
You're Alex, aren't you?
你是怎么知道我名字的?
How do you know my name?
因为你和你母亲长的很像
Because you look like your mother.
我母亲已经死了
My mother is dead.
我相信他们是这么和你说的
I'm sure that's what they told you.
快走吧 Alex!
Get going, Alex!
你给我闭嘴
Keep your mouth shut.
你们的电是从哪里来的?
Where do you get electricity?
我们有两个巨大的"仓鼠"来转动那个发电盘
We have two giant hamsters running on a massive wheel
-我们地下有个秘密的兽穴  -这真有趣
-at our secret underground lair.  -Yeah, that's funny.
冰箱里还有一些剩菜 你自便吧
There's leftovers in the refrigerator.Help yourself.
很抱歉我喜欢吃禽类
I ate most of the dark meat. Sorry.
我好久没品尝鸡的味道了
I never really appreciated chicken until right now.
我知道你要这么做 John
I know you think you need to do this, John,
但如果你炸了我的潜艇
but if you blow up my submarine,
我就要遇到很大的麻烦了
I'll have a big problem with my people.
你这是在奉劝我不要这么做吗?
Is that supposed to be an incentive not to blow it up?
我出生在这个岛上
I was born on this island.
没有几个人和我是一样的
Not many of my people can say that.
大多数人都是因招募而被带到这里来的
Most of them were recruited and brought here.
他们越爱这座岛
And as much as they love this place,
就越会不惜一切代价来保护这座岛
as much as they would do anything to defend it,
他们需要知道他们能离开这里
they need to know they can leave if they want to.
而那艘潜艇维系着他们的希望
The sub maintains that illusion.
那你是在欺骗他们
So you're lying to 'em.
不 他们是自愿留下的
No. They're here because they want to be here.
有些人只是还没有完全接受
Some of them are just not ready to make a full... commitment yet.
但你 John...
But you, John...
你已经做出了选择
You've already made that commitment,
而现在你有一个选择
and now you have a choice.
停下好好想想
Because if you stop and if you think,
我能给你看样东西
I can show you things...
那样你想了很久的东西
things I know you want to see very badly.
让我说的明白一点
Let me put it so you'll understand.
想象一下这里有个盒子
Picture a box.
你很了解盒子的 是吗 John?
You know something about boxes,don't you, John?
如果我告诉你在这座岛的某处
What if I told you that somewhere on this island
有一个巨大的盒子
there's a very large box,
无论你怎么想象 无论你希望那里面是什么
and whatever you imagined,whatever you wanted to be in it,
当你打开它时 它就会出现在你的眼前
when you opened at box,there it would be.
你怎么说 John?
What would you say about that, John?
我说那个盒子里最好是一艘新的潜艇
I'd say I hope that box is big enough to imagine yourself up a new submarine.
-你为什么这么愤怒John?  -因为你在撒谎
-Why are you so angry, John?  -Because you're cheating.
你和你的人
You and your people
能无限制的和外界联系
communicate with the outside world whenever you want to.
你们来去自如
You come and go as you please.
你们用电和水 还有枪
You use electricity and running water and guns.
你是一个伪君子
You're a hypocrite, a Pharisee.
你不配生活在这岛上
You don't deserve to be on this island.
如果你真的知道这个地方的奇妙之处
If you had any idea what this place really was,
你就不会把鸡放进你的冰箱了
you wouldn't be putting chicken in your refrigerator.
你才来了80天 John
You've been here 80 days, John.
我的一生都在这座岛上
I've been here my entire life.
是什么让你认为你比我更了解这座岛的?
So how is it that you think you know this island better than I do?
因为现在坐在轮椅上的人是你
Because you're in the wheelchair,
而不是我
and I'm not.
遇到什么麻烦了吗?
Did you have any problems?
现在照我说的做
Okay, here's how this is gonna work...
她要带我去潜艇那里
she's gonna take me to the sub.
一到那里 我就放她走
Once we're there, I let her go.
John你可以让她走了
John, she's done enough.
让我带你去吧
Let me take you.
我不想让你拖累我
I don't want you to slow me down.
快 我们走
Come on. Let's go.
John 在你走之前 你应该知道...
John, before you go, you should know...
Jack和我做了笔交易
Jack and I made a deal.
不到一小时内他就会离开这里的
In less than an hour he's leaving this island
而那艘潜艇只是单程的
on that submarine,and it's a 1-way ticket.
异常现象破坏了我们的通讯系统
The anomaly wiped out our communications.
我们和外界失去了联系...
We have no way of contacting the outside world...
那意味着一旦潜艇出发
Which means when that sub leaves,
它就永远回不来了
it can never come back.
你炸毁它也好
So whether you destroy the submarine
让它走也好 都是一个结果
or whether you let it go,the end result is the same
没人会找到这座岛的
no one will find this island.
我们走
Let's go.
快点
Come on.
你知道他是在操纵你对吗?
You know he's manipulating you, right?
怎么说?
How's that?
我父亲就是这样的人
That's what my father does.He manipulates people.
他能操纵别人
He manipulates people.
他让你感觉那是你的主意 其实那是他的
He makes you think it's your idea,but it's his.
那我要牢记在心了
I'll have to keep that in mind.
潜艇就在那儿...
Submarine's down there...
在码头的尽头
At the end of the dock.
我很抱歉把你圈进来
I'm sorry I had to involve you in this.
我知道你不欠我什么
Look, I know you don't owe me anything,
但我需要你最后帮我一次
but I need to ask you for one last favor.
你还想怎么样?
You don't knock?
你要放了我的朋友
I need you to let my friends go
在我走之后
after I'm gone.
如果我说不 那会阻止你走吗?
And if I said no,would that stop you from leaving?
当然会的
Of course it would.
你的朋友只是来救你的
Your friends are only here to rescue you.
而你好像是在挽救你自己 那么...
But you seem to be doing a good job of rescuing yourself, so...
我也没有理由把他们留在这儿了
I suppose there's no reason to keep them here.
你能保证吗?
Do I have your word on that?
我保证
You have my word.
你走之后我一定会放了他们的
I'll let them go just as soon as you've left the island.
我想就这样了
Well, I guess this is it.
谢谢你遵守你的诺言 Ben
Thank you, Ben,for keeping your promise.
站在那里别动!
Hold it right there!
把手举起来!
Get your hands up!
趴下!我说趴下!
Get down! I said get down!
你在这里干什么 John?
What are you doing here, John?
我很抱歉 Jack
I'm sorry, Jack.
为什么?
Sorry for what?
你干了什么?
What did you do?
告诉我不是你干的
Tell me you didn't do it.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
告诉我你没有杀那个孩子
Tell me that you didn't kill that kid!
什么?
What?
你认为我和Peter的死有关吗?
You think I had something to do with Peter's death?
我告诉你结束这一切
I tell you to end things with his mother,
接下来 他就死了!
and the next thing you know, he's dead!
John请你冷静一点
John, now calm down, please.
想想你自己说的 我为什么要杀Peter呢?
Think about what you're saying.Why would I kill Peter?
他盯上你了!
He was on to you!
我干这行很久了 我不会害怕一个毛头小子的
I've been doing this for a long time.I'm not sweating some rich kid.
那为什么你还在这里?
Then why are you still here?
-你的意思是?  -我让你离开这里
-What do you mean?  -I tell you to leave.
你告诉我你会离开的
You tell me you're gonna leave town.
为什么你还在这里?!
Why are you still here?
听着John 老实对你说
Now listen, John,I'll be honest with you.
我没有兑现诺言
I didn't end it.
我想干下去
I was looking for an angle.
我想在我退休前捞一笔
I wanted to make some money before I skipped out.
但后来发生了这事
But then all this happened.
Peter死了 一切都落空了
Peter died, and everything just went straight into the tank.
她受到很大的打击
She's devastated.
她取消了婚礼
She's called off the wedding.
已经无利可图了 John
There's no profit in it, John.
我是一个骗子 但不是杀人犯
I'm a con man, not a murder.
她取消了婚礼?
She called off the wedding?
她说她做不到
She said she couldn't deal with it.
她需要独自面对
She needs to be alone.
如果我现在打电话给她
So if I were to call her right now,
这就是她要告诉我的?
that's what she would tell me?
电话就在那边 John
Phone's right over there, John.
她的号码是...
What's her numb...
Locke我们知道你不想听到这个消息 但是...
Mr. Locke, we know this isn't what you want to hear, but...
你父亲逃走了
Your father's gone.
他去了墨西哥 在你们那次相遇后...
We know he fled to Mexico shortly after your...
然后就消失了
encounter, then he disappeared.
我很抱歉 他也许在这个世界的任何地方
I'm sorry, but he could be anywhere in the world right now.
好了 探长们 今天就到此为止
All right, detectives,that's enough.
Locke先生 今天有活干了
Mr. Locke has work to do today.
如果有什么消息我们会通知你的
We'll let you know if anything develops.
今天我们有好多事要做
We have got ourselves quite a day ahead of us, my friend.
你终于可以起床了
It's finally time to get you up out of that bed.
不 我不想
No. I don't want to.
这可没有选择
I don't remember asking.
现在
Now...
大多数人一开始都不想坐这玩意儿
Most people struggle with this at first,
但别担心
but don't worry.
你会习惯的
You'll get used to it.
不 求你了 我做不到
No, please. I can't do this.
你从八楼摔下来 并幸存了下来
You fell eight stories and survived.
我不想听到 有什么你做不到的
I don't want to hear about what you can't do.
好了
Now let's go.
会没事的
It's gonna be all right.
一切都会好的 John
It's gonna be fine, John.
-来吧  -不 我不能...
-Come on.  -No, I can't...
很好
You're fine...
行了
There we go.
行了 伙计
There you go, buddy.
看见了?
See?
也没那么糟 不是吗?
Wasn't that bad, was it?
我一会儿就回来 伙计
Be right back, buddy.
John你真的说到做到了
Well, John,you've really gone and done it now.
你不必装的很失望
You don't have to pretend to be disappointed anymore.
我们都知道你想让这一切发生
We both know you wanted it to happen.
这就是为什么你留下了Sayid包里的C-4
That's why you left the c4 in Sayid's bag
因为你想让这一切发生
Because you wanted me to make it happen.
拜托你解开他 Richard
Uncuff him, please, Richard.
你会做傻事吗?
You gonna do anything stupid?
不 先生
No, sir.
你还记得吗?John 当你叫我骗子的时候...
Do you remember earlier, John,when you called me a cheater...
当你说我不配待在这岛上的时候...
When you said I didn't deserve to live on this island? Well, get this--
当我和Jack握手的时候
There I was, shaking hands with Jack
我想方设法不让他离开这座岛
and thinking I'd give almost anything to come up with a way to stop him from leaving,
因为如果他离开的话
because to let him go
那会是一个软弱的信号 一个失败的信号
would be a sign a weakness,of failure, of defeat.
我的人都看在眼里
My people would see that.
他们会知道的
They would know it,
然后John 所有的错误都会归咎于我
and that, John, would be the end of me.
但如果我杀了他...
But to kill him...
那才是欺骗
That would be cheating,
因为我的人知道 我许下诺言
because my people also heard me make a promise,
如果我打破诺言...
and to break my word...
他们还是会归咎于我的
that would be the end of me, too.
而这时你出现了 John...
And then you came striding out of the jungle, John...
并实现了我的梦想
to you make my dream come true.
你不是又想和我说那个神奇的盒子了吧?
You're not gonna start talking about the magic box again, are you?
不John 我要带你去看那里面到底有什么
I'm gonna show you what came out of it.
当我那时问你 你是否很痛苦
When I asked you earlier if it hurt
当你忍受伤痛时 你一定误解我的意思了
when you suffered your injury,I think you misunderstood me.
很明显 当一个人被扔下高楼
It seems fairly obvious that when a person's back smashes
背部撞击地面时
into a hard surface after being thrown from a building,
会有很强烈的剧痛
that's gonna sting a little.
但我问的不是肉体上的伤痛
But I really wasn't asking about the physical pain.
你想知道那是否伤了我的感情?
What, do you want to know if it hurt my feelings?
不John 我想知道当你亲身父亲
No, John.I wanted to know what it felt like
想要杀你时你的感受
when your own father tried to kill you.
他就是你要炸毁潜艇的原因 是吗?
He's the reason you destroyed the submarine, isn't he?
你害怕了
You're afraid.
你怕他了 而这是唯一一个他找不到你的地方
You're afraid of him, and this is the one place he can never find you.
这是唯一他来不了的地方
This is the one place he can never get to.
你想要我做什么?
What do you want from me?
我不知道这是怎么发生的...
I don't know how it happened...
但你能和这座岛交流 John
But you seem to have some communion with this island, John,
而这让你变的特别重要
and that makes you very, very important.
你不知道自己在说什么
You have no idea what you're talking about, of course,
但经过一段时间你会更好的去理解事物的
but in time you'll have a better understanding of things.
那么我想要什么呢?
So what do I want?
我想帮助你 John
I want to help you, John.
为什么?
Why?
因为我在轮椅上 而你不是
Because I'm in a wheelchair,and you're not.
你准备好了吗?
Are you ready to see?
===================================
本字幕由YYeTs美剧翻译组制作
YYeTs美剧首发网站www.YYETS.com
===================================
爸爸?
Dad?